[{"answer": "Nice try.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 16, "question": "Do you think personally think homosexuality is a sin?", "qSentId": 15}, {"answer": "It's a valid question and my answer is: nice try.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 19, "question": "That's a valid question, isn't it?", "qSentId": 18}, {"answer": "I think I'm a pussycat.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 43, "question": "Are you harmless?", "qSentId": 42}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 45, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 44}, {"answer": "Great fun.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 64, "question": "It's fun, isn't it?", "qSentId": 63}, {"answer": "Thank you.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 69, "question": "-- provocative, my kind of girl, right?", "qSentId": 68}, {"answer": "No, of course, politicians seek power.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 87, "question": "-- want power?", "qSentId": 86}, {"answer": "What happened was it was like a three or four step process.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 106, "question": "But why is it?", "qSentId": 105}, {"answer": "He tried.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 122, "question": "Why didn't you do anything about it?", "qSentId": 121}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 124, "question": "Over eight years?", "qSentId": 123}, {"answer": "The Democrats pushed this politically or rather financially suicidal loans on the banks, literally allowing unemployment benefits to be used as collateral.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 134, "question": "-- blame the Democrats for an eight year regime which does nothing about?", "qSentId": 133}, {"answer": "They did.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 140, "question": "Why didn't your team do something about it?", "qSentId": 139}, {"answer": "I can't stand them.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 158, "question": "What do you think of the bankers now who were bailed out awarding themselves multi -- multi-million dollar bonuses?", "qSentId": 157}, {"answer": "Well, technically what --", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 163, "question": "Why is your instinctive gut reaction to everything I say, even when I'm agreeing with you, why is it always to mention the Democrats?", "qSentId": 162}, {"answer": "No, what I'm saying --", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 166, "question": "Are you like programmed like a robot?", "qSentId": 165}, {"answer": "Well, I would say that there are a lot of similarities to the French Revolution --", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 221, "question": "-- where is the similar mob to Mussolini's and Hitler's in the modern democratic era?", "qSentId": 220}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 223, "question": "The Tea Party?", "qSentId": 222}, {"answer": "No, they're much closer to the original Tea Party which -- and actually not as -- not as much of a rabble as the original Tea Party, which, as I point out, the Founding Fathers weren't wild about the original Tea Party, curiously enough, because they were so against mobs.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 226, "question": "The nearest thing to it in America?", "qSentId": 225}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 231, "question": "Oh, the current Tea Party?", "qSentId": 230}, {"answer": "They're smarter than any liberal.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 242, "question": "Well, a lot -- a lot of them aren't the brightest of sparrows, are they?", "qSentId": 241}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 244, "question": "Do you think so?", "qSentId": 243}, {"answer": "Yes, I do and I --", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 246, "question": "Do you really think that?", "qSentId": 245}, {"answer": "-- meet them and I speak to them and they get my jokes -- which already makes them smarter than the average liberal.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 248, "question": "In your heart?", "qSentId": 247}, {"answer": "Well, it makes them smarter than the average liberal.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 250, "question": "So that's why you like them, because of their smiles?", "qSentId": 249}, {"answer": "Putting crosshairs on people's heads --", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 261, "question": "What do you think she's said that's inflammatory?", "qSentId": 260}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 265, "question": "Is that inflammatory?", "qSentId": 264}, {"answer": "The P.R. is darling.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 281, "question": "Every single time I ask you a question, rather than answer about Sarah Palin and crosshairs, you instinctively go, what about the Democrats?", "qSentId": 280}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 303, "question": "Would you encourage them to carry on doing it?", "qSentId": 302}, {"answer": "-- to shoot up a shopping mall.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 306, "question": "How do you know?", "qSentId": 305}, {"answer": "Because we know that he's out of his mind.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 308, "question": "How do you know?", "qSentId": 307}, {"answer": "Well, what if I --", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 314, "question": "Then what would you think?", "qSentId": 313}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 344, "question": "Do you still think that?", "qSentId": 343}, {"answer": "Well, no.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 346, "question": "Do you really?", "qSentId": 345}, {"answer": "I haven't the first idea.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 368, "question": "You probably know, don't you?", "qSentId": 367}, {"answer": "I wouldn't if I were in her shoes, not for president -- maybe senator or something.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 370, "question": "Do you think she should?", "qSentId": 369}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 377, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 376}, {"answer": "No, she's fabulous.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 384, "question": "Is she dangerous?", "qSentId": 383}, {"answer": "No, I think she's terrific.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 386, "question": "You don't see any fault line in Sarah Palin?", "qSentId": 385}, {"answer": "Well --", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 403, "question": "Why -- if you see it as such a low down profession, why are you so obsessed with it?", "qSentId": 402}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 411, "question": "And you sleep until noon, is this right?", "qSentId": 410}, {"answer": "Well, that's when I get up early.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 413, "question": "That's a bit weird, isn't it?", "qSentId": 412}, {"answer": "It's out today.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 433, "question": "Will you stop the shameless plugs?", "qSentId": 432}, {"answer": "Yes, I mean, the -- this is the difference between, among many others, among Democrats and Republicans on this.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 447, "question": "Should he resign?", "qSentId": 446}, {"answer": "Well, last week, they're -- your network --", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 458, "question": "-- who is defending -- allow me to -- who's defending women?", "qSentId": 457}, {"answer": "What mobs do is create -- and I have a chapter on this.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 477, "question": "Is he fabulous?", "qSentId": 476}, {"answer": "You're joking.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 487, "question": "Who attacked Breitbart?", "qSentId": 486}, {"answer": "I was traveling all -- all week last week, just a copy out at the beginning.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 490, "question": "Who seriously, on mainstream media, attacked him?", "qSentId": 489}, {"answer": "No, basically the entire mainstream media.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 495, "question": "I mean, because there's not a massive onslaught, is it?", "qSentId": 494}, {"answer": "Now, you're taking this very long question which I'm trying to give an answer, which is so contradicting --", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 532, "question": "-- ever calm down?", "qSentId": 531}, {"answer": "I don't know who exposed Mark Sanford.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 534, "question": "On Mr. Breitbart, is it not understandable people might be at least skeptical given his track record?", "qSentId": 533}, {"answer": "Good.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 538, "question": "Why didn't the Republicans expose Arnold -- Arnold Schwarzenegger?", "qSentId": 537}, {"answer": "Nobody said why, damn that \"L.A. Times\" for exposing this, I don't believe it.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 541, "question": "Arnold Schwarzenegger?", "qSentId": 540}, {"answer": "-- because he has to hold a press conference because the photos came out.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 571, "question": "-- what's he still doing there?", "qSentId": 570}, {"answer": "Do you hallucinate about someone who --", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 605, "question": "Do you hallucinate the liberals, seriously?", "qSentId": 604}, {"answer": "I never get angry.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 608, "question": "-- clearly sees the world and you aren't grasping it, so you get angry and frustrated and attack that person?", "qSentId": 607}, {"answer": "Because Anthony Weiner said publicly in an interview with Wolf Blitzer, \"I was hacked.\"", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 612, "question": "OULTER: -- doing a story on hacking last week?", "qSentId": 611}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 618, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 617}, {"answer": "Don't talk about either engagements, Social Security number, age or anything else.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 636, "question": "You're 50 in December, are you?", "qSentId": 635}, {"answer": "I don't answer questions about myself.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 640, "question": "You have never deliberately put the wrong age on a document?", "qSentId": 639}, {"answer": "I would be fine with it.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 669, "question": "How would you react?", "qSentId": 668}, {"answer": "I can't imagine being married.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 672, "question": "Would you?", "qSentId": 671}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 704, "question": "Do you wish you hadn't said it?", "qSentId": 703}, {"answer": "It was because something was happening that week.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 713, "question": "Do you feel that?", "qSentId": 712}, {"answer": "My responsibility is for making fun of Bill Maher, or making fun of I suppose liberals for not reacting to Bill Maher, for saying this horrible thing about Dick Cheney.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 722, "question": "You're still responsible for your words, aren't you?", "qSentId": 721}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 735, "question": "Yeah?", "qSentId": 734}, {"answer": "The difference is if you read this in the full analytical context of where I wrote it, it was manifestly intended as a joke.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 745, "question": "What is the difference?", "qSentId": 744}, {"answer": "The same place I did when I ran for president last time around, which is I'm pro-life and proud to be so.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 768, "question": "Where do you stand on abortion?", "qSentId": 767}, {"answer": "That's correct.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 770, "question": "But you weren't always pro-life?", "qSentId": 769}, {"answer": "Well, Ronald Reagan was also pro-choice and then became pro-life.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 781, "question": "How do you -- how do you counter that, given your view has changed so dramatically on that one issue?", "qSentId": 780}, {"answer": "Well, the issue of great significance that everybody tells me I should just change my mind on and -- and do the politically expedient thing, which is to say that my health care plan was a terrible mistake, I'm not willing to do.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 788, "question": "On how many issues can you do it before you lose credibility?", "qSentId": 787}, {"answer": "I've always been in favor of preventing discrimination against people, whether they are homosexual or -- or straight...", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 790, "question": "Gay rights?", "qSentId": 789}, {"answer": "And at the time when I ran for office, I made that very clear.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 806, "question": "Yes, but given that most gays would like the right now to legally get married in -- in many states, you are not in favor of all gay rights, are you?", "qSentId": 805}, {"answer": "-- the gay community -- the gay community changed their perspective as to what they wanted.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 814, "question": "Am I right?", "qSentId": 813}, {"answer": "Well, equal rights in -- in employment, equal rights in -- I mean, for instance, as -- as the governor, I had members of my team that were gay.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 822, "question": "What -- what is the gay rights that you're in favor of?", "qSentId": 821}, {"answer": "You know, I -- I -- I still feel quite distinctly matters of personal faith from the leadership that one has in a -- in a political sense, I..", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 826, "question": "Does your faith mean that you view homosexuality as a sin?", "qSentId": 825}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 829, "question": "Can you do that?", "qSentId": 828}, {"answer": "You -- you don't begin to apply the doctrines of a religion to responsibility for -- for guiding a nation or for guiding a state.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 832, "question": "Seriously?", "qSentId": 831}, {"answer": "You know, that's something that you can take up with the church.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 834, "question": "What is the Mormon position on homosexuality being a sin?", "qSentId": 833}, {"answer": "Nice try, but I'm not going to get into --", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 848, "question": "Do you personally think homosexuality is a sin?", "qSentId": 847}, {"answer": "It's a valid question and my answer is nice try.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 850, "question": "That's a valid question, isn't it?", "qSentId": 849}, {"answer": "I'm going to tell you that as a -- as a leader of the American people, I will do everything in my power to treat all people with respect and dignity and to -- and to advance the rights people have to choose their own course in life.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 853, "question": "Nice try at what?", "qSentId": 852}, {"answer": "Well, I -- I'm not quite sure what -- what you're referring to...", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 865, "question": "If you were made president, you wouldn't make any pronouncements whatsoever of a personal nature about any form of personal behavior?", "qSentId": 864}, {"answer": "Well, you know, after 42 years of marriage, you know a person pretty -- pretty well.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 889, "question": "Given that so many politicians, at the moment, are being hit by scandal, anything we don't know about Mitt?", "qSentId": 888}, {"answer": "Well, for sure, I hope it was me, because --", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 893, "question": "Were you each other's first proper partners?", "qSentId": 892}, {"answer": "-- as a senior in high school.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 900, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 899}, {"answer": "He dated all of my girlfriends.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 906, "question": "Would you like to elaborate on this?", "qSentId": 905}, {"answer": "I was extremely wary.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 909, "question": "Seriously?", "qSentId": 908}, {"answer": "Now it -- now it's all coming out.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 913, "question": "Don't I wish?", "qSentId": 912}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 917, "question": "Have you ever drunk alcohol?", "qSentId": 916}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 919, "question": "You don't -- you've never taken drugs?", "qSentId": 918}, {"answer": "Of course not.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 922, "question": "And presumably, we never -- you never had an affair, because you couldn't have done it?", "qSentId": 921}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 924, "question": "And you can say that with total non-Schwarzenegger certainty?", "qSentId": 923}, {"answer": "It better not.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 930, "question": "So this is a -- I would say this is one of your trump cards, because when you look at all these politicians at the moment, whether it's Anthony Weiner or it's John Edwards or it's Arnold Schwarzenegger, the one thing we don't have to worry about in America if you're elected president is anything tumbling out of the -- the cupboard, right, Ann?", "qSentId": 929}, {"answer": "That's right.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 939, "question": "Well, you suffer from multiple sclerosis?", "qSentId": 938}, {"answer": "And breast cancer, as well.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 941, "question": "And you -- and you've also had to fight cancer?", "qSentId": 940}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 951, "question": "Would you -- would you go along with that?", "qSentId": 950}, {"answer": "Definitely.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 954, "question": "He's a man of passion?", "qSentId": 953}, {"answer": "Well, my -- my sons, unfortunately, refer to something known as a Mitt-frontation.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 961, "question": "And, I mean, do you want to join in with Here, Mitt?", "qSentId": 960}, {"answer": "Oh, yes.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 964, "question": "So you can lose your temper?", "qSentId": 963}, {"answer": "You know, I -- you know, I will say as both of us have gotten older, you certainly hope you mature.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 968, "question": "Quite explosive when he goes?", "qSentId": 967}, {"answer": "Oh, Ann is the -- the Mitt stabilizer.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 973, "question": "But what do they also call -- what do they call me?", "qSentId": 972}, {"answer": "It doesn't worry me.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 987, "question": "That must worry you, doesn't it?", "qSentId": 986}, {"answer": "You know, I really don't think many people in this country make their vote based upon someone's religion.", "docId": "110607pmt", "aSentId": 994, "question": "And Governor, if -- if America managed to bring itself to vote for its first ever African-American president, do you believe that the mood now is right to potentially vote for its first Mormon president?", "qSentId": 993}]